Anne-Elise Chung

INTERACTION DESIGNER

Combining an architectural background with UX skills to design and develop immersive user-centered experiences. Passionate about visual storytelling.



anne-elise.me

aelichung@gmail.com (626) 348-9900 Santa Clara, CA

PROJECTS

DESIGN & DEVELOP Ongoing

virtual bonsai

Grow and sculpt your own bonsai tree, in a relaxing virtual environment. Created using Blender and Unity for Google Cardboard and for the web.

More Info

UX UI & FRONT-END 2018 (8 weeks)

houseplant

An online plant store for people with black thumbs. I designed, tested, and developed an e-commerce site to help people plant shop confidently.

More Info

UI & CONSTRUCTION 2015 (10 weeks)

striptease

I worked in a team of 20 to create a provocative installation, blending both physical and digital design. I lead the design for the user interface, as well as helping with construction and design. The installation show was attended by over a hundred people and warmly received.

More Info (striptease gallery link)
Youtube Video

EDUCATION

UX DESIGN PROGRAM 2017-present

Bloc

BACHELOR OF ARCHITECTURE 2010–2015

California Polytechnic State University San Luis Obispo

WORK EXPERIENCE

CAD CONSULTANT 2017-present

WDA (Warner Design Associates)

Providing CAD training, project support and technical assistance.

TECHNICAL DESIGNER 2015–2017

EDG Interior Architecture and Design

Worked with construction team, engineers, and clients to create luxury hotels and restaurants.

TOOLS & KNOW-HOW

UX Design

Draw.io, Balsamiq, User flows, User stories

Digital Prototyping/Research

Sketch, Figma, Invision, Usabilityhub, Maze

Developer Skills

HTML, CSS, Javascript, C#, jQuery, Firebase, Git

3D Design & Rendering

Unity, AutoCAD, Rhino, SketchUp, Blender, Revit, V-Ray

Adobe CC

Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Lightroom, Premiere

Physical Prototyping

3D printing, lasercutting, working with wood/metal/plaster/resin etc.

SERVICE

UX / UI / FRONT-END 2018-present

Code for San Jose

TUTOR 2018-present

Read Santa Clara

VP OF EDUCATION 2017–2018

Toastmasters Novato